TURNING ROUGH MARKDOWN INTO A
DECK USUALLY MEANS REWRITING THE
SAME CONTENT INSIDE PRESENTATION SOFTWARE.
SLIDE BUILDER SKIPS THAT COMPLETELY:
WRITE ON THE LEFT,
AND THE DECK RENDERS LIVE
ON THE RIGHT.
IT KEEPS THE FORMAT DEAD
SIMPLE TOO — SLIDE BREAKS
WITH THREE DASHES,
TITLES WITH # OR ##
— SO IF YOU ALREADY
HAVE CONTENT IN THE HOUSEHOLD’S
EXISTING SLIDE CONVENTION,
IT DROPS STRAIGHT IN.
WHAT MAKES IT USEFUL IS
THAT THE STYLING DECISION IS
FAST INSTEAD OF PRECIOUS.
YOU CAN MOVE THE SAME
WORDS THROUGH SIX HAND-BUILT LOOKS,
FROM MINIMALIST AND TERMINAL TO
COUNCIL SIGNAL,
AND SEE IMMEDIATELY WHICH ONE
FITS.
THEN WHEN IT’S READY,
EXPORT THE WHOLE THING AS
A SINGLE HTML FILE WITH
THE CSS AND JAVASCRIPT BAKED
IN.
NO DEPENDENCIES,
NO HOSTING REQUIREMENTS,
NO “WORKS ON MY MACHINE”
PROBLEM — JUST SEND THE
FILE AND THE DECK OPENS
OFFLINE.
IT EVEN KEEPS YOUR DRAFT,
TITLE, AND CHOSEN TEMPLATE IN LOCALSTORAGE,
SO YOU CAN COME BACK
WITHOUT LOSING THE THREAD.
SLIDE BUILDER TURNS “I HAVE
THE CONTENT” INTO “I CAN
SHARE THE DECK” IN ONE
PASS.